iboobo.com 2012-10-08

# Iboobo Web Design - Web Traffic | SEO | Web Design

**Accountability**  
1. iboobo.com will be responsible for all personal data collected. All personal data collected will be used and processed fairly and lawfully while in our possession or custody. iboobo.com ensure all our customers that we would be accountable for our organisation's compliance to our Privacy Policy.

**Specifying Purposes**  
2\. Personal data collected, will not be used for a new purpose unless we obtain consent from our customers. iboobo.com are the sole owner of the personally identifiable information collected on this site. iboobo.com collect personally identifiable information for the sole purpose of registering a user for our web site

**Consent**  
3\. iboobo.com do not collect sensitive information from our customers. iboobo.com assure all customers that all personal information collected would be used or disclosed only for the purposes for which it was collected.

**Limiting Collection**  
4\. Only the necessary personal data is collected from customers’ for business purposes. Both the amount and the type of data collected shall be limited to that which is necessary to fulfill the purposes identified.

**Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention**  
5. iboobo.com will not disclose, share, transfer, sell or rent personally identifiable information to any 3rd party. iboobo.com do not send unsolicited marketing email to our customers. Customers will occasionally receive email on special promotions iboobo.com hold. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, users may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email.

6. iboobo.com do not keep personal data for longer than is necessary for those purposes for which they are collected.

7. iboobo.com have developed guidelines and implemented procedures to govern the destruction of personal data that are no longer required to fulfill the identified purposes.

8. iboobo.com do not use "cookies", “web-bugs” or any other tracking technologies to collect information from users of our web site.

9. iboobo.com would not display or make publicly available, whether through online directories, customer lists or otherwise, the personally identifiable information collected.

**Accuracy**  
10. iboobo.com ensure our customers that all personal information collected is accurate and kept up to date. iboobo.com do not maintain duplicate copies of personal information in different systems.

**Safeguards**  
11. iboobo.com ensure our customers that appropriate security safeguards are in place to protect personal data against unauthorised access, misuse, disclosure, copying, use, alteration, accidental loss or theft, destruction or damage.

12\. Only authorised personals have access to our systems. Consultants, contractors or other temporary employees do not have access to the data.

**Openness**  
13\. Our data protection policy (Privacy Policy) is displayed on the web site and the policy is set out in the same language medium as the web site. iboobo.com encourage all our customers to read our Privacy Policy to understand the our objective of collection their personal data.
